{
	"cards": [
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-32-tag-multiple-choice-card-1",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"connective tissue that supports the skeleton.",
					"bones and voluntary muscles of the body.",
					"nervous system’s control over the muscles.",
					"involuntary muscles of the nervous system."
				],
				"question": "The musculoskeletal system refers to the:",
				"source": "See Introduction"
			},
			"back": "bones and voluntary muscles of the body."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-32-tag-multiple-choice-card-2",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"traction.",
					"stabilization.",
					"reduction.",
					"immobilization."
				],
				"question": "The act of pulling on a body structure in the direction of its normal alignment is called:",
				"source": "See Specific Musculoskeletal Injuries"
			},
			"back": "traction."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-32-tag-multiple-choice-card-3",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"metaphyseal",
					"greenstick",
					"epiphyseal",
					"diaphyseal"
				],
				"question": "A(n) __________ fracture occurs in the growth section of a child’s bone and might lead to bone growth abnormalities.",
				"source": "See Musculoskeletal Injuries"
			},
			"back": "epiphyseal"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-32-tag-multiple-choice-card-4",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"guarding.",
					"ecchymosis.",
					"swelling.",
					"deformity."
				],
				"question": "Common signs and symptoms of a sprain include all of the following, except:",
				"source": "See Musculoskeletal Injuries"
			},
			"back": "deformity."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-32-tag-multiple-choice-card-5",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"Dislocation",
					"Strain",
					"Sprain",
					"Fracture"
				],
				"question": "A ____________ is a musculoskeletal injury in which there is partial or temporary separation of the bone ends as well as partial stretching or tearing of the supporting ligaments.",
				"source": "See Musculoskeletal Injuries"
			},
			"back": "Sprain"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-32-tag-multiple-choice-card-6",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"pelvis.",
					"femur.",
					"hip.",
					"humerus."
				],
				"question": "Traction splints primarily immobilize and secure fractures of the:",
				"source": "See Specific Musculoskeletal Injuries"
			},
			"back": "femur."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-32-tag-multiple-choice-card-7",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"Blood vessels",
					"Diaphragm",
					"Heart",
					"Skeleton"
				],
				"question": "Which of the following structures is regulated by smooth muscle?",
				"source": "See Anatomy and Physiology of the Musculoskeletal System"
			},
			"back": "Blood vessels"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-32-tag-multiple-choice-card-8",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"lymphocytes.",
					"blood cells.",
					"platelets.",
					"electrolytes."
				],
				"question": "Bone marrow produces:",
				"source": "See Anatomy and Physiology of the Musculoskeletal System"
			},
			"back": "blood cells."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-32-tag-multiple-choice-card-9",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"In most cases, compartment syndrome develops within a few minutes after an injury.",
					"Most cases of compartment syndrome occur following a severe fracture of the pelvis.",
					"Compartment syndrome occurs because of increased pressure within the bone cavity.",
					"Compartment syndrome typically develops within 6 to 12 hours after an injury."
				],
				"question": "Which of the following statements regarding compartment syndrome is correct?",
				"source": "See Compartment Syndrome"
			},
			"back": "Compartment syndrome typically develops within 6 to 12 hours after an injury."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-32-tag-multiple-choice-card-10",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"When distal circulation and neurological functions are absent",
					"If transport time to the hospital is greater than 20 to 30 minutes",
					"If resistance is encountered or the patient experiences severe pain",
					"If a traction splint will be used to immobilize the injured extremity"
				],
				"question": "In which of the following situations should the EMT splint an injured limb in the position of deformity?",
				"source": "See Emergency Medical Care"
			},
			"back": "If resistance is encountered or the patient experiences severe pain"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-32-tag-multiple-choice-card-11",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"tendons.",
					"cartilage.",
					"ligaments.",
					"fascia."
				],
				"question": "Skeletal muscle is attached to the bone by tough, ropelike fibrous structures called:",
				"source": "See Anatomy and Physiology of the Musculoskeletal System"
			},
			"back": "tendons."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-32-tag-multiple-choice-card-12",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"muscle decreases in size and function because of disease or trauma.",
					"carbon dioxide, lactic acid, and other wastes accumulate in the muscle.",
					"increased use of skeletal muscle causes an increase in its strength.",
					"the tendons that attach muscle to bone become stretched or injured."
				],
				"question": "Atrophy is a condition that occurs when:",
				"source": "See Anatomy and Physiology of the Musculoskeletal System"
			},
			"back": "muscle decreases in size and function because of disease or trauma."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-32-tag-multiple-choice-card-13",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"leave the toes exposed.",
					"use a pillow as a splint.",
					"observe for tissue swelling.",
					"apply a pneumatic splint."
				],
				"question": "When splinting a possible fracture of the foot, it is most important for the EMT to:",
				"source": "See Specific Musculoskeletal Injuries"
			},
			"back": "leave the toes exposed."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-32-tag-multiple-choice-card-14",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"connective",
					"striated",
					"smooth",
					"involuntary"
				],
				"question": "Skeletal muscle is also referred to as __________ muscle.",
				"source": "See Anatomy and Physiology of the Musculoskeletal System"
			},
			"back": "striated"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-32-tag-multiple-choice-card-15",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"comminuted",
					"greenstick",
					"pathologic",
					"transverse"
				],
				"question": "A fracture caused by minimal force that is associated with diseases such as cancer and osteoporosis is called a __________ fracture.",
				"source": "See Musculoskeletal Injuries"
			},
			"back": "pathologic"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-32-tag-multiple-choice-card-16",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"Skeletal",
					"Autonomic",
					"Smooth",
					"Cardiac"
				],
				"question": "Which of the following types of muscle is under direct voluntary control of the brain?",
				"source": "See Anatomy and Physiology of the Musculoskeletal System"
			},
			"back": "Skeletal"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-32-tag-multiple-choice-card-17",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"Striated muscle tissue is attached directly to the bones by tough bands of cartilage.",
					"It forms the major muscle mass of the body and usually crosses at least one joint.",
					"Striated muscle is involuntary because you have no conscious control over it.",
					"Most of the body’s striated muscle is found within the walls of the blood vessels."
				],
				"question": "Which of the following statements regarding striated muscle is correct?",
				"source": "See Anatomy and Physiology of the Musculoskeletal System"
			},
			"back": "It forms the major muscle mass of the body and usually crosses at least one joint."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-32-tag-multiple-choice-card-18",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"Pelvis",
					"Femur",
					"Hip",
					"Humerus"
				],
				"question": "Which of the following fractures has the greatest potential for internal blood loss and shock?",
				"source": "See Specific Musculoskeletal Injuries"
			},
			"back": "Pelvis"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-32-tag-multiple-choice-card-19",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"radius and ulna.",
					"clavicle.",
					"scapula.",
					"midshaft femur."
				],
				"question": "The most commonly fractured bone(s) in the body is the:",
				"source": "See Specific Musculoskeletal Injuries"
			},
			"back": "clavicle."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-32-tag-multiple-choice-card-20",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"Open fractures of a long bone",
					"Multiple closed long bone fractures",
					"Nondisplaced pelvic fracture",
					"An amputation of an extremity"
				],
				"question": "Of the following musculoskeletal injuries, which is the least severe?",
				"source": "See Musculoskeletal Injuries"
			},
			"back": "Nondisplaced pelvic fracture"
		}
	],
	"category": {
		"value": "chapter-32",
		"label": "Chapter 32"
	},
	"tags": [
		{
			"value": "multiple-choice",
			"label": "Multiple Choice"
		}
	]
}